belgocontrol.be 2014-04-03

# Belgocontrol - Privacy Policy

BELGOCONTROL (“we”, “us”, “our”) provides the information set out on the www.belgocontrol.be website (the “Website”) solely for information purposes.

Your use of the Website is governed by the Terms and Conditions. By using any part of the Website, completing any subscription with us and/or submitting any information to us on the Website, you agree that your personal information obtained through the Website may be held and processed in accordance with the Privacy Policy.

1\. INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE

You can visit the Website without giving us any Personal Information. However, if you wish to use the full range of services that we offer, you will need to complete the subscription process and than logon to the Website (using your subscription details) at each subsequent visit to the Website.

As part of the subscription process and at various other points on the Website we will need you to provide us with certain Personal Information. When you submit your Personal Information via the Website you may be asked to consent to the processing and transferring of your Personal Information as set forth in this Privacy Policy. If you would prefer that we not collect any Personal Information from you, please do not provide us with any such information. Please note, however, that if you choose not to provide us with your Personal Information you will not be able to access or use our full range of services.

We do not sell, share or transfer the Personal Information that you provide us through the Website except as set out in this Privacy Policy.

Except as otherwise described in this Privacy Policy, we use the Personal Information you provide us through the Website only for the purposes of processing your subscription and/or login details, processing any submission by you and responding to any comments or questions you have.

We may use the information you provide in aggregate (non-personally identifiable) form for internal business purposes, such as generating statistics and developing marketing plans. We may collect, store or accumulate certain non-personally identifiable information concerning your use of the Website, such as information regarding which of our pages are most popular to facilitate general website administration.

Please note that we may disclose any information, including Personal Information, we deem necessary in our sole discretion to comply with any applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental request.

Sensitive information is not sought through the Website. Sensitive information includes data relating to race or ethnic origin, political opinions, religious or other similar beliefs; trade union membership, physical or mental health; sexual life or criminal record. If you do provide sensitive information, you are thereby explicitly consenting to us using that information for the purposes for which it has been provided.

2\. TYPES OF INFORMATION WE COLLECT

2.1. Website subscription  
To subscribe to use the Website you must complete the online subscription form. During subscription you are required to give your contact information (such as your name, address, telephone number and e-mail address). This information enables us to process and fulfil your subscription online. Optionally you may also provide further information (such as the purpose for which you intend to use the data available on the Website). Upon completion of the subscription process we will send you an e-mail confirming your subscription.

2.2. Enquiry’s  
To send us an enquiry by e-mail you may supply us with your e-mail address. This e-mail address will only be used to respond to your enquiry.

3\. ACCURACY

We will take reasonable steps to create an accurate record of any Personal Information you have submitted through the Website. However we do not assume responsibility for confirming the ongoing accuracy of your Personal Information.

If you advise us that your Personal Information is no longer accurate we will, so far as practicable, make corrections. You can also request that your Personal Information be deleted from our systems at any time by e-mailing info@belgocontrol.be.

4\. ACCES TO YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

If you wish to acces Personal Information that you have submitted via the Website, please submit your request in writing to Belgocontrol – Communication – Tervuursesteenweg 303 – B1820 Steenokkerzeel Belgium. Any such request should be supported with a proof of identity (photocopy of passport or ID card)

5\. COOKIES

We may use session cookies in order to enhance the service we provide on our Website. A session cookie is a small data file sent from our Website to your internet browser, which is stored in the temporary memory of your computer (this file is erased when your browser is closed). A session cookie will allow us to track the pages that you have visited and thereby facilitate your use of the Website.

You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether or not to accept it.

6\. THIRD PARTIES

We may retain other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf in relation to the purposes set forth in this Privacy Policy. Examples include data analysis firms, customer support specialists, webhosting companies and software development or support companies.

Such third parties may be provided with access to your Personal Information if needed to perform their functions but may not use such information for any other purpose. Such third parties may be located in countries both inside and outside the European Economic Area (the “EEA”). Although countries outside the EEA may not require the same level of protection of Personal Information as countries within the EEA we always demand that third parties adhere to the same procedures that we follow ourselves with respect to your Personal Information, including this Privacy Policy.

7\. LINKS 

The Website may contain links to or from other websites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of other websites. This Privacy Policy applies only to the information we collect on the Website. We encourage you to read the privacy policies of other websites you link to or otherwise visit from our Website.

8\. SECURITY

We implement various security measures to protect the security of your Personal Information both on line and off line. If you have any questions about security at our Website, you can send an e-mail to info@belgocontrol.be.

9\. BUSINESS TRANSFERS

As we continue to develop our business we might sell certain of our assets or outsource certain business functions. In such transactions user information, including Personal Information, generally is one of the transferred business assets, and by submitting your Personal Information on the Website you agree that your Personal Information may be transferred to such parties in these circumstances.

10\. NOTIFICATION OF CHANGES

We may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we decide to change our Privacy Policy we will post the revised Policy here. As we may make changes at any time without notifying you we suggest that you periodically consult this Privacy Policy. Please note that, in the absence of your consent to changes in the way we use your Personal Information, our rights to use your Personal Information will be based on the Privacy Policy in effect at the time your Personal Information was collected.

11\. JURISDICTION

This Privacy Policy is construed in accordance with Belgian law, and by providing us with your Personal Information you submit to the exclusive jurisdiction of the Belgian Courts.
